[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 3]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
"Unsoiled Starlight"]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
[Bid Report for]
[Zhuoyuan Technology's Annual
Legal Services Project]
[Zhuo Yu'an]
I have to contact
my one-night stand for business.
Shu Tinglan, you really are something.
Hello?
Hello.
-This is...
-Hello.
Mr. Zhuo is in a meeting right now.
Leave a message, I can
pass onto him later.
I see.
This is Lawyer Shu Tinglan.
Please let Zhuo Yu—
Mr. Zhuo—
that I have some official
business with him?
Okay.
I'll pass on the message for you.
Okay, thank you.
Shu Tinglan,
what exactly are you expecting?
ZY.
Zhuo Yu'an.
[Accept Friend Request]
[Processing]
[ZYA]
[Inviting you to video call]
[Microphone: ON] [Speaker: ON]
[Camera: ON]
Are you looking for me?
Yes.
What is it?
[Microphone: ON] [Speaker: ON]
[Camera: ON]
Well.
I heard Zhuoyuan Technology
is planning to find
a long-term partner law firm domestically.
My firm, Hongzheng Law Firm,
is very experienced—
You call me just for this?
[Microphone: ON] [Speaker: ON]
[Camera: ON]
Rest assured.
All the clients handled by
our Lawyer Xiao—
Shu Tinglan.
As far as I know,
you're still an assistant
lawyer, aren't you?
Yes.
You—
how does Mr. Zhuo know that?
[Microphone: ON] [Speaker: ON]
[Camera: ON]
Lawyer Xiao sent a rookie like you
to negotiate a long-term
partnership with me.
Does he think Zhuoyuan Tech's
partnership isn't worth much?
Or does he think I, Zhuo
Yu'an, am easy to fool?
[Microphone: ON] [Speaker: ON]
[Camera: ON]
Is this the sincerity of
Hongzheng Law Firm?
No.
I understand.
Sorry to bother you.
Just as I thought.
A man's tenderness in bed
can't be taken seriously.
[Zhuo Yu'an]
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
Tinglan,
how's the Zhuoyuan progress?
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
I was just about to share the
good news with everyone.
This morning,
Zhuoyuan Tech contacted me
and said they're willing to give
Hongzheng Law Firm a chance.
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
Lawyer Xiao,
I'd like to join this project.
Mm, okay.
But Zhuoyuan Tech wants a colleague
familiar with corporate legal affairs
to liaise with them.
Tinglan has experience in this area.
She can participate in supporting work.
Mm.
Tinglan did well on the last case.
Keep up the good work.
Thank you, Lawyer Xiao.
Alright.
If there's nothing else today,
let's end the morning meeting here.
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
Tinglan,
Since Lawyer Xiao asked you to do it,
it means she trusts your ability.
When it comes to intellectual property,
if you have any questions,
you can ask me.
I know a thing or two.
Thank you, Lawyer Zhou.
You've got this.
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
Not going home?
Thanks.
Does Mr. Zhuo have anything else?
Work matters.
I'm very sorry.
You might not know me well yet.
My principle is to keep work
and personal life separate.
Besides,
your law firm was already
within Zhuoyuan's consideration.
Understood.
Please rest assured, Mr. Zhuo.
From now on, I'll keep my position clear
and do my job well.
But Lawyer Shu—
it's personal time now.
Does President Zhuo have two faces?
For you—
more than two.
You should save these words
to sweet-talk someone else.
There's no one else.
If I made you uncomfortable,
I apologize—as Zhuo Yu'an.
I'm going home.
It's too cold outside.
What's wrong?
Wrench.
Pliers.
Done.
Thanks.
Tomorrow I'll call a worker to fix it.
What are you doing?
I'm soaked.
Let me use your bathroom.
Over there.
Help!
What do I do when "rekindling
an old flame" turns into
It means he can't forget you and
wants something long-term.
No way.
He doesn't seem to have
shown that intention.
Then he's a player keeping you
on the hook.
Be careful not to fall into the trap.
A person can't—
at least shouldn't—get into
a murky relationship
with their own client.
It's a bit complicated.
I'll tell you later.
Anyway, be bold and express yourself.
Enjoy it.
Be bold and express yourself.
Shu Tinglan,
pass me a towel.
Oh, coming!
Why are you nervous?
I'm not nervous.
Not at all.
♪ Curved like your smile ♪
♪ Gently rising on tiptoe ♪
Actually, Mr. Zhuo,
why are you nervous?
♪ This preference, suddenly ♪
I'm not either.
Really?
♪ Blue, blue sky ♪
♪ Stars blinking ♪
♪ You by my side ♪
♪ How many times—how many times
have I missed you today ♪
Tinglan,
I—
Can I stay the night?
♪ Irreplaceable ♪
What do you want?
♪ You are the best encounter ♪
♪ I want to draw a circle around you ♪
Sure.
♪ So you won't wander far away ♪
As long as you don't mind
sleeping on the sofa.
♪ How lucky, of all the chances ♪
♪ The world is a paradise with you in it ♪
♪ Every adventure ♪
♪ Has you by my side ♪
♪ I want you to discover ♪
♪ This is no accidental moment ♪
♪ It's my little hidden scheme ♪
♪ I hope in every day and night ♪
♪ I can see your smiling face ♪
♪ Future and past ♪
♪ Written by you and me ♪
♪ One line, tied into a knot ♪
♪ Tied to every day of love ♪
You're up so early
♪ Every moment now ♪
♪ With you and me, become forever ♪
Weren't you sleeping in the living room?
When did you sneak in?
It's really cold outside.
♪ How many times—how many times
have I missed you today ♪
Alright then, I'll go sleep
in the living room.
No, don't.
♪ Irreplaceable ♪
I'll go.
♪ You are the best encounter ♪
♪ I want to draw a circle around you ♪
♪ So you won't wander far away ♪
♪ How lucky, of all the chances ♪
♪ The world is a paradise with you in it ♪
There's a blanket by the sofa.
Okay.
♪ Every adventure ♪
Thank you.
♪ Has you by my side ♪
So he has this side to him too.
♪ I want you to discover ♪
♪ This is no accidental moment ♪